Jackie Dube

Junior Web Developer

23 Grens Road, Kempton Park West, Gauteng 1619 jackienomsa3@gmail.com 067 076 9436 View portfolio

I am a 27 year old self taught web developer. I am a hard worker, I pay attention to every detail and I always aim for the best result in any and every job I do because everything I do and achieve is a reflection of me. I have experience in the hospitality industry, the retail industry and sales, however I am interested in computer programming and I have acquired several web development and programming skills. I am a fast learner and I have come to realize that there is nothing I cannot do once I put my mind to it.

With the skills I have acquired, I hope to utilize and improve them in a professional environment. I have knowledge on both the frontend(JavaScript, React, HTML and CSS) and the backend(Python, Django and MySQL).

Work Experience

Business Development Executive

Public Sector Indaba - Kempton Park, Gauteng January 2018 to March 2020

My job involved telesales to government and private entities, booking accommodation, boardrooms and conference rooms, and also host the events

Sales Assistant

Outdoor Warehouse March 2016 to November 2017

Waitress

September 2014 to January 2015

Packaging staff

LSG

November 2013 to July 2014

Education

Future flyers academy July 2015 to October 2015

Oxford Combined College

December 2013

Skills

SOFTWARE SKILLS

Python, Django, Flask, SQL (MySQL, PostgreSQL), HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Materialize <u>View portfolio</u>

GENERAL COMPUTER SKILLS

Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, Outlook

Certifications/Licences

Drivers License Code 10

September 2016 to September 2021 Code 10